http://www.aami.com.au/privacy.html

Your browser version is no longer supported, so you may experience issues while using this site. Please upgrade to a current browser to enjoy the best experience.
Home
Privacy
Online Terms &  Privacy Statement
Privacy is important especially when you consider the number of ways we communicate and interact these days. We are committed to our privacy obligations and will conduct our business to ensure the protection of your personal information, including sensitive information.
It is important to understand that our companies provide a wide range of financial services and products and our companies may use and disclose your personal information in different ways.
Read our Group Privacy Policy – Suncorp Group Privacy Policy (including list of countries)
Online Terms and Conditions
Making a Privacy Complaint
AAMI Social Media Guidelines
AAMI SmartPlates Privacy Statement
AAMI SmartPlates Terms and Conditions
AAMI General Insurance
For Policy holders:
AAMI General Insurance Privacy Statement: applies to AAMI general insurance customers including those holding Car, Home, Travel, Caravan, Motorcycle policies and AAMI Business Insurance
AAMI NSW CTP Insurance Privacy Statement
AAMI SA CTP Insurance Privacy Statement
AAMI ACT MAI Insurance Privacy Statement
For non-Policy holders involved in a claim:
General Insurance Privacy Statement
AAMI NSW CTP Insurance Privacy Statement
AAMI SA CTP Insurance Privacy Statement
AAMI ACT MAI Insurance Privacy Statement
All other situations such as social media, competitions, Skilled Drivers, and general enquiries
AAMI Life Insurance
For Policy holders:
AAMI Life Insurance Privacy Statement: applies to Life Insurance customers
Updating your marketing preferences
You can update your marketing preferences the following ways:
Contact us via email
Call us on 13 22 44.
AAMI Health Insurance
AAMI Health Insurance Privacy Statement
Pet Insurance
Dog Insurance Privacy Statement
Puppy Insurance Privacy Statement
Cat Insurance Privacy Statement
Indoor Cat Insurance Privacy Statement
PRODUCTS
COOKIE AND DATA POLICY
We use cookies and other related technologies to improve and tailor your website experience. See our Cookie and Data Policy. This policy provides information about how AAMI collects and uses data related to your online activity, and how you can choose to remain anonymous.
AAI LIMITED TRADING AS AAMI
AAMI Home Building and Home Contents Insurance, Landlord Insurance, Strata Insurance, Car Insurance, Motorcycle Insurance, NSW and SA CTP Insurance, ACT MAI Insurance, Caravan Insurance, Business Insurance and Travel Insurance are issued by AAI Limited ABN 48 005 297 807 AFSL 230859 (AAI) trading as AAMI. Registered Office, Level 28, 266 George St, Brisbane QLD 4000.
Information provided is general advice only and has been prepared without taking into account any person's particular objectives, financial situation or needs. Read the relevant Product Disclosure Statement or Policy Document available at www.aami.com.au and consider whether it's appropriate for you before making any decisions about whether to buy or continue to hold a product.
AAMI PET INSURANCE
Pet Insurance is issued by The Hollard Insurance Company Pty Ltd (ACN 090 584 473; AFSL 241436) (Hollard); distributed by Pet Insurance Pty Ltd (ACN 607 160 930; AR 1234944) (PIPL) and PIPL's authorised distribution partners (including Platform Ventures Pty Ltd (ABN 626 745 177; AR 001266101) (Ventures) under the AAMI brand); and administered by PetSure (Australia) Pty Ltd (ACN 075 949 923; AFSL 420183) (PetSure). PIPL and Ventures are authorised representatives of PetSure. PIPL and PIPL's authorised distribution partners (including Ventures) will receive a commission which is a percentage of the premium paid to Hollard and PetSure may receive a portion of the underwriting profit, if any - ask PetSure for more details.
Close
AAMI HEALTH INSURANCE
AAMI Health Insurance is issued by nib health funds limited ABN 83 000 124 381 (nib), a registered private health insurer, and is marketed by Platform CoVentures Pty Ltd ABN 82 626 829 623 (PC), a Suncorp Group company. PC is an authorised agent of nib and receives commission from nib.
AAMI LIFE INSURANCE
AAMI Life Insurance products, other than in some circumstances the Redundancy Benefit, are provided by either Asteron Life & Superannuation Limited ABN 87 073 979 530, AFSL 229880 (Asteron) or by TAL Life Limited ABN 70 050 109 450 AFSL 237848 (TAL Life) which is part of the TAL Dai-ichi Life Australia Pty Limited ABN 97 150 070 483 group of companies (TAL). Both Asteron and TAL Life are part of the TAL Dai-ichi Life Australia Pty Limited ABN 97 150 070 483 group of companies (TAL). TAL companies are not part of the Suncorp Group. TAL companies use the AAMI brand (brand of the Suncorp network) under licence. Redundancy Benefit issued on or before 31st March 2020 was offered by AAI Limited ABN 48 005 297 807, AFSL 230859 (AAI) trading as AAMI which is part of the Suncorp Group. New Redundancy Benefit policies and renewals offered from 1st April 2020 will be issued by Asteron Life & Superannuation Limited, ABN 87 073 979 530, AFSL 229880 (Asteron). The different entities of TAL and the Suncorp Group of companies are not responsible for, or liable in respect of, products and services provided by the other. Any advice on this page in connection with the Life products is general in nature and is provided by Platform Ventures Pty Ltd ABN 35 626 745 177 AFS Representative Number 001266101 (PV). PV is part of the Suncorp Group and an authorised representative of TAL Direct Pty Limited ABN 39 084 666 017, AFSL 243260 (TAL Direct). General advice does not take into account your individual needs, objectives or financial situation. Before you decide to buy or to continue to hold a Life Products you must read the relevant Product Disclosure Statement.
